はい…
よう
動くな…
私だ…
だ 誰！？
忙しそうだな
ヒーモヒモヒモ
けど急いだ方がいいわね
一体 どこから…
はい では失礼します
働き者は俺ぁ好きだがね
勿論全力で調べておりますわ
親子そろって大間抜け
けれど一切 情報がありませんの
-ヒーモ
-何よこれ！
情けない限りで申し訳ありません
君にしては仕事が遅いのではないか
ですから 不法入国者の線で今…
行様のところから
テープを盗み出してきたか…
その写真の子が俺ぁかわいくてね…
肝心なところが変な歌で
重ね録りされてるじゃない
息子の恋人について
調べろと言ったはずだ？
これじゃ何のために危険な橋を渡って
あの娘の価値が
他のやつらにもれる前に…
他の人間にも彼女の事を
調べられたら面倒だもの
ええ ささいな情報でも入り次第必ず…
あんたみたいなハエがまわりを
ブンブン飛んでると気になるんだ…
ヒーモヒモヒモヒーモヒモー
Moooch mooch moochie moooch moocher.
いいね 忠告はこの１回だけだ
Investigation Report
shall report the findings of my investigation.
regards to the conduct of his partner, known by the alias "Nino"
(henceforth referred to as "Nino").
Moooch mooch moochie mooo—
その子にだけはとまるんじゃない
What is this?
じゃないと
The most important part got taped
over with some weird song.
殺すよ
ひぃぃっ！
Why did I risk so much to steal this
from Master Ko in the first place?!
な はっ 何なのよ… は…
Incoming
Ichinomiya Seki
Hello?
今の…
It's me.
“See her?” “No I don't”
You're taking longer with
this task than I expected.
I thought I asked you to
investigate my son's girlfriend.
“Now you see her Now you don't”
ほらみんな夢中だ
regards to the conduct of his partner, known by the alias "Nino"
Investigation Report
I'm doing everything I can.
COSMOS vs ALIENの戦い
いつでもマーベラス
However, there is a severe lack of information.
艦隊率いるあいつはまさしく
生まれる前からエイリアン
I cannot apologize enough.
I will continue the investigation
assuming she's an illegal alien.
ミクロとマクロの距離感大事
Of course. I will be sure to report
any new findings right away.
宇宙規模での勘違いだけどね
Yes. Very well, goodbye.
アダムとイブの再来ならば
猫もしゃくしもいっそ
このままでいんじゃない？
Like idiot father, like idiot son.
Still, I should hurry.
ほら もっとよく見て
There'll be real trouble if anyone
else starts looking into her.
ほら もっと欲張って
I need to finish before someone finds
out just how valuable she is.
ほら そっと手を取って
ほら とっとと笑って
Hey.
You look busy.
I have a soft spot for hard workers.
トークトークのBPMは
とうにジョークの域を越えて
Don't move.
Wh-Who are you?
How'd you get in here?
山超えて 谷超えて
あいつのいる星に届く
I care deeply about that girl in the picture.
ほらきっと霧中だ
キャプテン・クィーンにSOS
ミサイル迎撃準備よし
It really bugs me when flies like you
go buzzing around her head.
弾道操るあいつはいかにも
生まれる前からエイリアン
You follow me? This will be your only warning.
いままさに宇宙は SPACE
Don't even think of landing on her, fly. Or else...
いわゆるひとつのSWEET
甘い甘い宇宙のTASTE
I'll kill you.
いわゆるひとつのSWEET
魔法をひとふり あの子と二人きり
砂糖をひとふり あの子はいただき
What was that... just now?
Chapter 144: "Cryptanalysis"
Hey, Nino!
よっ ニノ
Chief.
村長
What are you doing out so late?
どうした こんな夜中に
I have something for you.
お前に届け物があってな
What is it? Cookies?
何だ クッキーか？
No.
いんや
This came for me today.
今日 俺んところに届いた
Nino... it won't be long now.
ニノ… いよいよだ
え～ 今の話を踏まえて
With that in mind, I'd like to go over
the company's current direction.
今後の運営を話し合いたいわけだが
As you can see on the graph in front of you,
手元のグラフを
見てもらえばわかるように
the key to increasing revenue
in our Hong Kong branch is...
香港支社の売り上げを上げるカギは…
manufacturing a new line of
shoes and school slippers.
土足かつ上履きを使用した
生産ラインを使い
This will lead to us landing on the rug.
カーペットへの着地成功にいたる…
Consequently, sales in the Venusian demographic
should increase, causing tables in Japan to rise...
そして金星層の売り上げは上昇し…
日本国内のテーブルも徐々に
-迫り上がっ
-あ！
What are you doing, Nino?!
一体何なんですか！ ニノさ～ん！
What's wrong? You're acting really strange.
どうしたんですか！？ おかしいですよ
You've never done something this
meaningless and confusing.
今までこういう意味のなさすぎる
行動はしなかったのに！
ふん！
Wait, no.
いやそうだった
Nino never does anything for no reason.
ニノさんは意味のない事はしない
So there must be some reason
she's acting this way.
きっとこの行動にも何か意味があるんだ
It's my job to decipher it.
俺が読み解かなきゃ
She put her school slipper on my head.
上履きを俺の頭の上に置く…
School slipper?
上履き…
An apparatus she uses to walk on the ground.
それはニノさんが地面を
踏み締めるための道具…
Does that mean...
て 事は…
あっあ…
She wants to step on me?
踏ませろ…？
Oh no... has Maria been having
some kind of influence on her?
まさかマリアさんの影響を
受けてしまったという事か？
Um, Rec...
あ あのなリク…
That's awful! No wonder it's so hard
for her to come out and say it!
何て事だ… どうりで
言いにくそうなわけだ…
But if this is how Nino has decided
to express her love...
しかしそれが！ ニノさんの愛情表現なら
I, uh...
実は そのな…
I'll endure it!
俺は…
耐えてみせる！
I'll make myself LOVE being stepped on!
喜んで踏まれてみせるぞ！
I got a message from my parents.
両親から連絡がきてな…
え ご両親から…？
Your parents?
Ah... I see.
あぁ なるほど…
Why do I feel kind of disappointed?!
何で俺は今ちょっと残念なんだ！
Rec was more worried about what he'd
found lurking in his own subconscious.
ニノの発言より 己の深層心理からの
カミングアウトの方が
強烈だったリクでした…
Chapter 145: "All of a Sudden"
って えー！？
Your parents?!
ご両親！？ ニノさんの！？
The message just reached his brain.
今やっと脳に届いたようですな
Indeed.
Could you come by my place later?
後で私の家の方に来てくれないか？
I missed my chance last time, but now I'd
like to talk to you about those tapes.
以前できなかった
カセットテープの話がしたいんだ
わ わかりました　今すぐ行きます
All right. Why don't we go right now?
Takai, Shimazaki—do you mind if we
end the meeting a little early?
高井 島崎 打ち合わせは
今ので大丈夫だよな？
Of course, it's fine.
ええ 大丈夫でございますぞ
Then that's all for today. Sorry.
じゃあ悪いが今日はこれで解散だ
But...
でもやっぱり
As a loyal secretary, it still makes me cry.
ちょっぴり涙が出ちゃう
だって秘書だもん…
Shimazaki, let's go out and have a drink!
島崎 今日は飲まんか！
I feel like bawling my heart ou— Where'd she go?
とことん泣きたい気分…
あ いない…
Partypooper...
いけずぅ！
Her parents have finally contacted her?
This is what I've been waiting for!
両親からの連絡…
私はこれをずっと待っていたのよ…
If only those bugs I'd planted were still active,
I wouldn't have to take such risks myself.
盗聴器が生きてれば
こんな危険な事しなくてすむのに…
But ever since that day,
they all stopped working...
あの日を境に 何者かに
全部外されてしまったのよ
I'll kill you.
殺すよ…
It'll be okay... I'm sure he was just bluffing.
大丈夫よ はったりだわ
There's no way someone would kill me over this...
殺すなんて そんな事いくら何でも…
Hey! Watch out!
-あ！ あぶない 君！
-あっ！
Sister and Maria's joint-operation snare
is that way! The Death Trap!
その辺はシスターくんと
マリアちゃんのコラボ作品
デストラップが！
えっ？ 死の！？
Death? Is he seriously trying to kill me?!
まさか本気で殺す？
うわぁ！
うわぁぁぁっ！
Keep it together.
おい君 しっかり！
Don't let go of your pride.
プライドを手放しちゃいけないよ
Maria came up with this trap to
destroy a person's will to live.
これはマリアちゃん考案の
心を殺すためのトラップだからね
Just pretend everything you just went
through was nothing but a bad dream.
今 自分の身に起こった事は
全て悪夢だと思うんだよ
って ダメだわ
早く行様達を追わないと！
No, I have to go after Master Ko and the girl!
おや 君はリクくんの秘書の
Oh, you're Rec's secretary,
aren't you? Shimazaki, right?
島崎さんじゃないですか
おお～ 一応スーツ着といてよかった
I'm so glad I wore a suit for no real reason.
He's Master Ko's subordinate...
この人 行様の部下の
Mr. Shirai...
白井さん…
You remembered my name. I'm honored.
光栄だな 覚えていてくれましたか
But it's dangerous to walk around this area alone.
お１人でここを歩かれるのは危険ですよ
Let me see you to the edge of the riverbank.
河川敷の外までお送りします
いっ いいえ
私はまだ少し用がありますから
That's okay. There's something I have
to take care of down here first.
I see.
そうですか
Well then, please take care.
ではどうぞ お気をつけて
I will.
Why is my heart fluttering like this?!
ダメよ 何をときめいてるのよ私
いいのは顔だけでしょ！
He's cute, but that's all!
Guys like him are usually just mindless
workaholics who can only...
ああいう男は大抵仕事しか能がない
ボンクラって決まって…
あら？
Why is he walking around with that line marker?
あの人 何で
ラインマーカーなんて引いて歩いて…
Could it be? Is he laying out
a safe path for me to follow?!
まさか！ はぁっ
何も言わず私のために… 安全な
帰り道を引いてくれているの！？
なっ 何て人…
What a man!
My knight in shining powder!
白線に乗った王子様
Shimazaki found herself caught
in her very own Love Trap.
島崎が勝手に
ラブトラップにかかりました
S-So, Nino... what did you want to talk about?
そ それでニノさん
話って何でしょうか…
Well, see...
ああ… その実はな…
ひっ怖い！ 怖すぎる！
This is just too scary!
I have to stand my ground on this one!
俺がどっしり構えてないといけないのに
But the longer I have to wait,
the more nervous I get!
待たされれば待たされただけ
恐怖心がふくらむ…
これぞ
It's like having to get a flu shot!
“インフルエンザ注射の法則” だ…
To be honest... I kind of... lied
to you about something.
実は私はお前に…
ひとつ嘘をついてるんだ…
Oh, well... I mean, I know all about that.
え… そんな…
そんな事はもちろん知っているけども
Is that what's been bothering
her this whole time?
まさかニノさん
そんな事でずっと悩んで…
Did you think we'd drift apart from each
other if I knew you'd lied about that?
じゃ じゃあニノさんは… その嘘のせいで
俺が離れていくと思ってたんですか？
Is that it? I don't care about that.
何だ！ そんな事なら全然
I keep thinking, but I can't figure it out.
たくさん考えてもわからないんだ
I just don't know where to go from here.
私がこれからどうすればいいのかも…
I can't seem to figure out the answer on my own.
私１人で考えたんじゃ答えが出ないんだ
Will you hear me out?
だから聞いてくれるか
I want to put my heart in your hands.
私のハートをお前に預けたい…
S-Sure, of course you can.
ええ… そりゃあもちろん
I responded without hesitation, but the
Chief's words went through my head.
そう返事してしまった後に
あの時の村長の声が頭に響いた
The human heart is both heavy and fragile.
人間の心ってもんは 重い上に割れもんだ
It's okay. I've already accepted that lie about her.
だ 大丈夫… だってそんな嘘は
もうとっくに受け止めてた事だし…
わ 私はな…
I...
I have to leave the riverbank.
この河川敷から出て行かなきゃいけない
That had already been decided long
before you wound up down here.
お前が橋の下に来るずっと前から
出て行く事は決まっていたんだ
You're leaving?
出て行く…
When my heart slips through her
fingers and shatters into pieces...
受け止めてもらえずに
落下していく俺のハートは
底についた時
What kind of sound will it make?
一体どんな音で割れるのだろう
What do you mean you're leaving?
出て行くって どういう…
Where could you possibly go?!
河川敷から出て
どこに行くって言うんですか！
The sound of a heart...
受け止めてもらえなかった俺のハートが
Mute
when it shatters into pieces.
I'm going home.
帰るんだ
Where's "home"?
帰るってどこに！？
Some people can hear it.
聞こえる人には聞こえる
Mute
That sound a TV makes, even when it's muted.
テレビの電源が入っている時
Mute
Some people call it...
人はあの音を
Naturally, it's...
それはもちろん
Mute
Venus.
金星だ
The static sound of insanity.
電波の音と呼ぶ
Chapter 147: "Decisions"
The energy from the lingering effects of
the expansion of the Caspiose Nebula
今だったらカスペオーゼ星雲の
膨張の余波エネルギーで
have made it possible to return using even
a Mormay-class rocket right now.
モルメークラスのロケットでも
帰る事ができるんだ
あぁ もちろんファンドネル星の
重力の影響でワープはできないが
Obviously I can't warp there directly thanks
to the gravity well around planet Fundel,
but it shouldn't be a problem if I can
go into cryogenic hibernation.
まあ コールドスリープしていれば
問題ないから
ああ… 大音量の電波の音が聞こえる…
Those crazy waves are
pumping out at max volume.
Mute
Um, so that's what you couldn't tell me before?
えーと それが…
ずっと言えなかった事ですか？
Yeah.
そうだ…
When I asked you to be my lover, I knew
I'd have to abandon you someday.
お前に恋人になれと言った時も
いつか別れる事になるってわかってたけど…
But I didn't realize then just how
much I'd want to stay with you.
お前と
離れたくなくなるなんて
そんな事はわからなかった…
I should have told you earlier, but I didn't
want things between us to end.
早く言わなきゃと思うのに
お前との暮らしを
終わりにしたくなくて…
I'm just being selfish. I'm sorry.
わがままだな… ごめんな
い ニノさん…
Nino...
What should I do? Nino's really
upset about all this.
どうしよう ニノさんは
深く思い悩んでいる
But it's Venus, right? Just don't
go back if you don't want to.
でも金星って
か 帰りたくないなら
帰らなきゃいいんじゃ
I do want to go back.
帰りたいんだ
I want to see my parents.
両親に会いたいんだ
But I also want to stay with you and
everyone else under the bridge.
でもお前とも一緒にいたいし
河川敷の皆とだって一緒にいたい！
Nino, please don't cry.
ニノさん！ な 泣かないで…
Oh, I'm crying?
お？ 泣いてるか？
Pull yourself together!
しっかりしろ俺！
You're the only one who can
stop Nino from crying!
今 ニノさんの涙を止められるのは
俺だけだろ
You need to be a man about this!
俺も男なら男らしく…
Nino!
ニノさん！
Recruit!
だからリクルート
Will you come to Venus with me? I can
give you a wonderful life there!
私と一緒に金星に来てくれないか？
絶対幸せにする！
Nino?
ニ… ニノさん
She's so manly.
男らしい…
"She might be the one," Rec thought to himself.
この人なら… リクはそう思ったという…
Chapter 148: "A Wonderful Venusian Life"
You want me to come to Venus?
って金星にですか！？
俺が！？
Yeah. I'm sure my parents will love you.
そうだ！
私の両親もお前なら気に入るだろう！
You want me to meet your parents?
ご両親に紹介って…
That sounds great, but... Venus?
そりゃ嬉しいですけど金星って…
You might never be able to return.
Make sure you think about this carefully.
行ったら戻ってこれないかもしれない
よく考えてくれ…
Nino's really serious about this.
ニノさん 本気で言ってる…
So I have to give her a serious answer.
俺も本気で返さなきゃ…
Even if her home is just some place
here on Earth called Venus—no!
帰る場所が金星という名の
地球上のどこかだとしても…
いや！
ニノさんは金星と言ってるんだから
Nino truly believes it's Venus, so I have to
seriously consider emigrating to another planet!
俺も本気で金星への移住を考えるんだ…
Venus
Ven us
Here we are, Rec.
さあ着いたぞリク
So this is Venus.
ここが金星か…
気を引き締めていかないとな
I'd better get my act together.
あら あの方新しいお隣さん？
Is that the new neighbor?
Look! He has a torso!
ヤダッ 胴体があるわ！
But his hair is so silky and dreamy!
毛もふぁっさふぁさだし
ミステリアスでステキ
Hello there. You must be Rec.
やあ君がリクくんか…
Let me be clear. I won't give my
daughter to just anyone—
言っておくがハンパな男に娘はやらな
My, you have a lovely pair of eyes.
何ていい目をしているんだ…
Welcome to the family!
君なら大歓迎だ… よく来てくれたな
あっはははは
Your father has so many arms.
腕の多いお父さんだ…
Yeah, that's definitely how I'd handle it.
うん まぁ 俺なら当然こうだな
No, wait! Considering how
Nino "welcomes" people...
いや待てよ！？ 歓迎と一口で言っても
ニノさんの歓迎の方法は
Like this!
こう！
Here parents might be even more extreme!
そしたら ご両親は
それ以上に…
A close encounter with the unknown!
ザ・未知との遭遇！
We come not only from different backgrounds,
but different planets entirely!
そうだ… 土地というか星から違うんだ
There's bound to be some cultural differences.
色々食い違う事もあるはず…
Breakfast time, everyone!
さあ皆さんごはんですよ…
My word, Rec. You can cook, too?
まぁリクさんってばお料理まで
Are all Earthlings as perfect as you?
地球人は皆
こんなにパーフェクトなのかい？
ぶはっ！
What's wrong?!
どうされました！？
You put too much miso in your soup.
この味噌汁濃い口じゃないか！
す すみません…
I'm really sorry. Was it not to your liking?
お口に合いませんでした！？
生まれが関東なもので…
I'm from Kanto, so that's just...
I guess you couldn't help it.
ま… まあ仕方ないわよねぇ
But you better use firm tofu, Rec. Understand?!
リクさん… でもお豆腐は
木綿にしてちょうだい 絶対よ！
What's wrong, Rec? You don't
have to force yourself to go.
どうしたリク
無理はしなくていいんだぞ！
No, I can do it!
いいえっ 行ける！ 行けます！
I'll...
俺の味噌汁
I'll make sure your parents love my miso soup!
ご両親に気に
入ってもらえるように努力します
Does that mean you'll come with me?
それは来てくれるという事か！？
あ… はい…
Yes!
But...
でも… だからさっきから
But... somehow, this...
It feels all backwards!
何か逆！
Every girl's dream of donning a snow-white
veil is about to come true for Rec.
純白のベールに包まれる
女の子の夢が叶ってしまいそうです
Chapter 149: "Engaged? Well Then..."
So you're really coming with me to Venus?!
そうか！ 来てくれるのか金星に！
Y-Yes.
はい
U-Uh, Nino?
えっ あの あ ニノさん…
Is this how you express your happiness?
これ喜びの表現ですか？
あぁっ？ てゆうか…
Actually, is this? Could it be?
あれ これって
もしかして…
Is this what they call being engaged?
婚約ってやつじゃないの！？
I think it's about a size 7...
７号くらいかな…
What's that? A rocket classification?
You wanna know more before we leave?
は？ 何だ？
ロケットの型番か？
知っておきたいのか？
Oh, n-no! It's nothing!
あいやいやいや こっちの話で…
What do you want, Hoshi?!
How long have you been here?!
何だ星 お前いつからそこに…！
さっと…
I did it!
とったど～！
What do you think you're doing with my
Nino's ring finger, you rotten starfish?!
俺のニノさんの薬指に
何て事しやがるこのヒトデー！
Ha! You snooze, you lose!
へ～んだ 早いもん勝ちだもんな！
I'll say hi to her folks on Venus for you!
俺も金星のご両親に挨拶に行くもんね！
You were eavesdropping?!
聞いてたのかよテメェ！
I heard everything!
聞こえちゃいました～！
けっ！ ニノさんはな
俺だけを呼んでくれて！
Nino invited me! Just me!
Are you sure, Hoshi? You wanna
come with us, too?
本当か星 お前も来てくれるのか！
Of course, Nino.
おうともよニノ…
And I'll play my favorite song—"Gimme
Your Daughter"—for your parents.
俺のとっておきソング
“お嬢さんをギブ・ミー” を
ご両親に披露するぜっ！
Oh, really?
おおお～ そうか！
Uh, Nino?
ちょっと… ニノさ
We want to go, too!
僕達も行きた～い！
Take us with you!
ニノちゃん一緒に連れてって～！
うっくっ…
A Venusian vacation?
金星旅行？
Sounds great! I want to go!
いいわね あたしも行くわ！
Do they have white lines on Venus?
金星に白線はあるかなぁ…
Hey, where'd you all pop out of?
ちょっ お前らいつの間に～！
My romantic getaway is turning
into some community field trip!
俺のロマン飛行が 町内会の小旅行に！
You guys...
おお… 皆！
Now I won't have to be away from anyone!
これで誰とも離れなくてすむぞ！
ばとっ！
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
ばんざい！
Don't press too hard, Nino.
You'll flatten out the bud...
ちょっとニノ！
そんなに刺激を与えたら芽が伸びちゃっ
あはっ！ もう～ ニノったら
そんなに嬉しいの？
Ahh, Nino. Are you really that happy about this?
Well, as long as it makes Nino happy...
まあ ニノさんが
あんなに喜んでるんじゃ仕方ないか…
ふむっ
I see.
うわっ！ また出た！
You again?!
I thought you had to go back to work!
あんた仕事場に
帰ったんじゃなかったのか！？
I'm done with the hardest
part, thanks to you guys.
お蔭様で山場は超えた…
まっ まさかあんたまで
金星について来る気か！？
Don't tell me you want to come with us to Venus.
Don't be stupid.
バカを言うな
I seriously doubt my body's ability to
adapt to the Venusian environment.
金星にこの地球人の体が
適応できるとは思えんし
Who knows what kind of
pathogens are lurking there?
未知の病原体も恐ろしい
Frankly, I'm amazed you could be so brave.
君達の勇気が信じられん思いだよ
You've thought this over quite a lot, haven't you?
俺以上に具体的に
検討してらっしゃったみたいですね…
But to think that she's returning to Venus...
しかし金星へ帰ってしまうのか…
Now I'll never be able to finish my latest
project, "The Venus Documents"!
私の新作「ドキュメント・オブ・ヴィーナス」
が完成できないのは無念だ…
Hey, what's with the notebook?
You've just been drawing this whole—
何ですかそのノート？
さっき何か描いて！
I'm going back to Venus!
I'm going
back
to venus
私は金星に帰る
Nino...
ニノさん！
I see.
やはりか…
うわぁ！
It's only moe like that because it's a rough draft!
その絵柄が萌え絵なのは
ネームだからだぞ
It's just easier for me since that's
how I usually draw at work!
普段描いている方が早いってだけで
The final drawings will be way more realistic!
もちろん原稿では劇画調に！
No, listen... that's not why I'm
looking at you like this.
いや この目はそんな理由じゃ
ありませんよ…
This is like the diary of a stalker!
そうじゃなくてこれ
完全にストーカー日記じゃないか！
Are you still chasing after Nino?!
お前まだニノさんに
付きまとってたのか！？
It's not stalking!
ストーカーじゃない！
It's sneaking!
スニーキングだ！
I even bought an oxygen tank so
I could track her under water!
水中にもボンベをしょって
行ったんだぞ！
Could you take that red-alert covert-ops
crap of yours up with Sister?
そういうエマージェンシーな話は
シスターとしてあげて下さい！
Jeez, everyone here is so...
全くどいつもこいつも…
-やぁ～い…
-わぁ～…
But I'm just glad that's all
there was to Nino's secret.
でも…
良かったな ニノさんの秘密が
あんな事で…
-わぁ～っ
-はっはっはー
I've never been too concerned with where I live.
俺は元々住む所にはこだわらないし
So now there's nothing to worry about.
これでもう心配事はなくなったな…
-えっ えっ
-ちょっとこっち来てリク！
Rec, get over here!
Nino's telling us about Venus!
ニノちゃんに金星の話聞こう～！
Venus sounds awesome!
すっごい所なんだって金星！
I'm coming... right now.
今…
行きます…
I have to add a lot more detail to this scene...
やはり… ここのシーンをもう少し
しっかり描きたいな…
I should bring a spare tank next time.
次はスペアのボンベも持って
潜ってみるか…
An hour's worth of oxygen wasn't nearly enough.
前は１時間分のエアーでも
足りなかったからな…
Chapter 150: "Arakawa Qwik-Skit Challenge"
Here comes a riddle!
Oh, sounds fun!
What do the followers of a
scandalized political leader...
have in common with Professor Pitt from the lab?
旅の終わりに想うもの
And the answer is—
Oh! Oh! I know!
They both have to deal with impeaching!
求めるだけの日々は過ぎる
What?
'Cause, see, one wants to impeach,
and the other was in-peach-ed.
冬を待たずにはしゃいでる
Impeach, in-peach. Professor Pitt,
like a peach pit in a peach. Get it?
赤いコートに包まれる君
You're an ass. Why would you just
blurt that out during their act?
さよなら迷宮days
W-Well, it just occurred to me...
So I thought... I mean...
気づけばThank you days
Oh～ good bye days
Hold on. It looks like you were wrong.
Hey, twins. What's the real answer?
What do the followers of a
scandalized political leader...
have in common with Professor Pitt from the lab?
And the answer is...
旅の始まり想うもの
They both look better without a head!
立ち止まらずに深呼吸する
ふたり明日を泳いでる
Miss Maria, have you seen Master Ko?
Why hello there, Takai.
It looks like your hair has decided
to pack up and move down south.
魚みたいに並び揺れる
Next time, on 7 BRIDGE x2!
辛いNo thank youです
Master Ko!
悲しいNo thank youです
Illustration: Makoto Tsuchibayashi
Oh no～ good bye days
謎かけします！
おっ なかなか渋いじゃねーか！
突然の政権交代とかけまして
研究所の受付にいた
木下さんとときま～す
その心は…
はいはいはいは～い
どちらもびっくりした！ じゃね
ぅわぁぁ！
え？ 何？
びっくりするのって
“大きな栗の木の下で～” だろ
ビッグな栗 びっくり～ってな
うっ うっ うっうぅ…
あ あれ？
最悪だなお前
先に答え言うやつがいるかよ
や… いや…
何かピンときちまってよぉ… つい…
待て！ どうやら違ぇようだぜ
おい兄弟！ 本当の答え言ってみな！
突然の政権交代とかけまして～
研究所の受付にいた
木下さんとときます～！
その心は
どちらも頭が全然役に立たない でした！
あは！
マリア様 行様を
見かけませんでしたかな？
あら 高井さん
貴方のおでこ もう毛穴さん達は
皆お引っ越しずみなのね
いやぁっ！
次回 「７ BRIDGE×２」
行様ぁぁ～！